hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
The smell is moving away...
I'm saved...
Who is?
Please wait!
The real deal... starts now!
My role now is to stall this person
as long as possible...
so I should've avoided big techniques
that could be self-defeating...
But it seems this isn't an opponent
easy enough to beat
without using my Secret Technique...
Here I go!
I just had surgery
and am not at my best...
But if it'd just be opening the first of the
Eight Inner Gates the Gate of Opening
I should somehow...
The first gate... The Gate of Opening...
Open!
Primary Lotus!
The impact of the kick
was suppressed by the bones...?!
That's some speed... But it's over.
Damn it... No matter how much I think,
I can't come up with any good strategies...!
I've had it... can't hold any further...
With me right in front of you,
you can't even howl like a loser...?
Huh?!
Die!
You're mine!
Don't you be smiling
before you're going to die!
What?!
Who're you?!
It seems you're an ally this time...
A Sand...
Shinobi...
ally of the Leaf!
Leaf Village's Ally Nation
the Ninja of the Sand
The Sand...?! Am I still drunk...?
Gaara of the Desert...
Gaara.
Is that who you are?
Digital Shrapnel!
Did he blow the finger tip bones...?!
Impetuous...
You...
When you fought me...
you had more speed and sharpness.
Easy to say...
It's not that I'm holding a grudge...
But on account of you,
I had kind of a tough time of it.
I see...
But... why you...?
I owe a lot...
to the Leaf.
Sasuke!
I heard that we'd made up
with the Sand traitors...
But to think you'd change
this abruptly...
It's not like we attacked the Leaf
for the fun of it...
It was an order...
In the same way
that I'm here now.
I see. The Fifth Hokage
asked the Sand...
It's a big help.
By the way...
has your sharpness gotten worse?
Huh?
Are you going to give up again
or something?
This time I'll do it for you!
Sorry, but I can't give up.
A man mustn't be protected
by a woman so...
As usual you're a guy who's annoying
with the man-and-woman stuff.
Even if you act tough it's totally obvious
that it's bravado, you idiot!
This time you're taking sides
with the Leaf, huh?!
You guys sure are busy
all over the place!
She uses Genjutsu
with the sound of her flute.
Right!
Cyclone Scythe Jutsu!
Blowing away the sounds of the flute
and being able to nail the opponent
with a physical attack.
To think she can attack and defend
with one hand...
Unlike me she has a nice Jutsu.
That woman's a natural enemy to me!
Has Ukon... just about caught him
according to the strategy?
Puppet, huh...?
You three had been approaching
together, right?
Two went on ahead.
You guys are weak so...
You idiot... These guys are
out of the ordinary!
Behind you!
I can't... move.
What's this guy?
I leave this to you, Sakon! Do it!
Where's the other one?
Hey! Who are you looking for?
That state... I know!
Be careful!
They enter the body and start to fuse!
It's too late.
This guy!
What's the matter, Sakon?!
It seems like...
your Jutsu didn't work...
on the puppet.
This is a puppet too?!
Let me tell you this.
We the Sand Shinobi
aren't as lax as the Leaf.
Moreover, don't be carelessly
approaching...
the Black Ant!
He was fearsome
when he was an enemy...
But to think he'd be this dependable
when becoming an ally.
Ow... I got careless.
Let me rest in your body for a bit.
Good-for-nothing guy...
Who are these guys?
This is their ability!
Although you were caught off guard...
you getting hammered
by that puppet play...
Well...
Its power and speed
are nothing special.
I won't be beaten
by the likes of such a toy.
And I was able
to heal my belly wound.
I don't have much Chakra left...
but well
these are opponents I should be able
to tear apart nevertheless.
Indeed it seems he's healed.
What a recovery ability he's got.
Ordinarily I'm not the one
who becomes the main body
so it's hard to move, damn it.
You sure are mocking us...
He's not an opponent
you can beat fighting head on!
We should retreat for now and...
We can't back down after having been
mocked you know.
Don't mess with me!
The Black Ant isn't a Mechanism
for attacking.
Primarily it's just for capturing.
And... Crow paired up with the Black Ant
is exclusively for attacking.
Hey you! Let me out!
Eat this!
Puppet Show...
Hey, let me out! Let me out!
Secret Black Move Iron Maiden!
The play is over.
She hid, huh...?
Or did she run away?
No... That couldn't be...
I just got here.
Briefly explain the present situation,
including an analysis of her ability
and battle style.
First off, her fundamental tactic is
ensnaring her opponent in Genjutsu
with the sound of her flute.
And then she delivers physical attacks
to that opening.
Demon Flute: Chains of Fantasia!
This is bad! Is this Genjutsu?
I can't move my body...!
I believe this was your last hand, right?
Unfortunately...
this is reversed checkmate!
You little rat!
She's a classic Genjutsu-style
distance range type.
Most likely she must've seen your Jutsu
and figured out immediately
that it wouldn't mix well
with her own Jutsu.
And it's two against one too.
She'll never appear before us again
until she casts her Genjutsu.
Sound, huh...?
Yeah...
Genjutsu generally appeal
to the five senses of people...
sight, hearing, smell, taste, and touch.
The type that uses hearing
is the most troublesome of them all.
After she cleverly takes a distance on you
and then hides...
you have no idea where the Genjutsu
will be cast from or when.
The idea is for us to already be cast
by the Genjutsu
by the time we've figured out where she is
by the sound of the flute...
Ouch...
In my opinion, we're at an
overwhelming disadvantage.
A battle with this type essentially
wouldn't even be worth talking about
without sensor types
like Kiba or Neji.
At this rate we'll get pushed into a corner
sooner or later.
— We should just retreat...
— Who asked for your opinion?!
I told you to just explain the situation.
Don't misjudge my power...
If she thinks
she's hiding well from me...
in a distance enough for the sound
of her flute to reach...
she's naive!
Summoning: Blade Dance
Cut!
All right...
I've made it this far.
It's about time for my Genjutsu...
Huh?
How about it?
It's done.
She's sure... pushy.
She's scarier than my mom.
Pretty good, huh?
But well...
I just have to be grateful
for this time... huh?
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
boku nanka ga shaberi kaketara meiwaku ni omou ka na
would you think it was a bother if I approached you?
sonna fuan o kakaete yuuki o dashite mita yo
despite my doubts I worked up my courage
umaku shaberenai boku no fukiyou na hanashi
my clumsy attempts with words
kimi wa mimi o sorasazu ni chanto kiite kureta yo
you listened without turning away
sore dake de boku wa ukarete shimau no sa
no wonder I get carried away by you
dakedo kimi wa boku nante nantomo omottenai yo ne
but you don't feel anything for me do you?
setsunai yo
I feel so sad
dakedo
but...
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
In my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
I got careless earlier
but it won't be like that now!
Now you please stand back.
I'm grateful for the help,
but his opponent will be me!
Next for sure
with my ultimate Lotus...!
Hey, why are you moving forward?
I'm his opponent!
Next episode
"Showdown of the Strongest! Gaara vs Kimimaro!!"